Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Additional Photographs 5917 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- N.J. Fish & Game Council Hearing - June 19, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  was b21f129 - 13 photographs
- N.J. Labor Press Award -- Jan. 1972 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  was b21f130 -- 2 photographs
- New Jersey Trapping Hearing -- 3/24/1983 (Box 36, Folder 42)
  was b21f131 -- 1 photograph
- New Member Class - March 1983 (Box 36, Folder 43)
  was b21f132 -- 1 photograph
- New School (Box 36, Folder 44)
  was b21f133 -- 1 photograph
- N.Y. Auction Minneapolis - Nov. 1971 (Box 36, Folder 45)
  was b21f134 -- 3 photographs
- New York Christmas Party -- Dec. 1977 (Box 36, Folder 46)
  was b21f135 -- 3 photographs
- New York City Rally -- 11/1975 (Box 36, Folder 47)
  was b21f136 -- 3 photographs
- New York Division Meetings -- 10/1977 (Box 36, Folder 48)
  was b21f137 -- 6 photographs
- Membership Meeting N.Y. Divisions -- 6/24/1980 (Box 36, Folder 49)
  was b21f138 -- 7 photographs
- N.Y. Nominating Meeting -- Fur & 150 -- 4/11/1984 (Box 36, Folder 50)
  was b21f139 -- 17 photographs
- N.Y. Sewing Mach. Attachments Contract - 8/1983 (Box 36, Folder 51)
  was b21f140 -- 5 photographs
- NY State Senior Citizens Council - 5/14, 15, 16/1984 (Box 36, Folder 52)
  was b21f141 -- 5 photographs
- Newspaper Design Class - 3/1978 (Box 36, Folder 53)
  was b21f142 -- 1 photograph
- Nominating Meetings - April 1972 (1) (Box 37, Folder 1)
  was b21f143 -- 26 photographs
- Nominating Meetings April 1972 (2) (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Nominating Meetings - 1975 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  was b21f144 -- 5 photographs
- Mr. O'Campo - 1971 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  was b21f145 -- 2 photographs
- Ocean Leather Negotiating Committee -- April, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  was b21f146 -- 1 photograph
- Ocean Leather Ratification -- 3/29/1979 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  was b21f147 -- 9 photographs
- Ocean Leather Safety Committee (Box 37, Folder 7)
  was b21f148 -- 3 photographs
- Harvey O'Connor Memorial Meeting - Nov. 1987 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  was b21f149 -- 3 photographs
- Office Photos (Box 37, Folder 9)
  was b21f150 -- 20 photographs
- Offray Negotiations - Dec. 1984 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  was b21f151 -- 7 photographs
- Offray Workers Organizing Campaign (Box 37, Folder 11)
  was b21f152 -- 3 photographs
- Ohio Meeting (Wildlife Campaign) Columbus - 1977 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  was b21f153 -- 9 photographs
- Ohio State Branch Meeting -- 10/23/1977 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  was b21f154 -- 2 photographs
- Ohioians for Wildlife Conservation Columbus - 6/18/1977 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  was b21f155 -- 3 photographs
- Opochinsky - Bramen (Box 37, Folder 15)
  was b21f156 -- 1 photograph
- Oregon Trapping Meeting - 12/1979 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  was b21f157 -- 2 photographs
- Organization Committee - 1962 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  was b21f158 -- 1 photograph
- Organizing Class, NY - Feb. 26, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  was b21f159 -- 16 photographs
- Organizing Class - Newark -- Feb. 27, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  was b22f1 - 4 photographs
- Packinghouse Local 711 P - Boonton (Box 37, Folder 20)
  was b22f2 -- 5 photographs
- Lester Pannacci Retirement - 11/1980 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  was b22f3 -- 5 photographs
- Park East H.S. Sewing Machines (Box 37, Folder 22)
  was b22f4
- Parsons (Box 37, Folder 23)
  was b22f5 -- EMPTY
- Parsons Tanning Contract -- 5/1974 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  was b22f6 -- 5 photographs
- Parsons Meeting -- March 1968 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  was b22f7 -- 9 photographs
- Parsons Tanning Picnic - Aug. 1968 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  was b22f8 - 4 photographs
- Parsons Tanning Picnic - Aug. 1970 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  was b22f9 -- 4 photographs
- Parsons Picnic -- Aug. 1972 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  was b22f10 -- 1 photograph
- Passaic General - Medical Exams (Box 37, Folder 29)
  was b22f11 -- 2 photographs
- Labor Leadership Assembly for Peace - 11/11/1967 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  was b22f12 -- 1 photograph
- Peace - labor Assembly Breakfast 1969 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  was b22f13 -- 1 photograph
- Peace Demonstration, Fur Market -- 10/15/1969 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  was b22f14 -- 4 photographs
- Peace Demonstration - Wash. - 11/15/1969 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  was b22f15 -- 3 photographs
- Peace Demonstration - City Hall - May, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  was b22f16 -- 19 photographs
- Labor Peace Meeting - March 23, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  was b22f17 -- 2 photographs
- Peace Demonstration - 4/24/1971 (Livingstone) (1) (Box 37, Folder 36)
  was b22f18 -- 21 photographs
- Peace Demonstration - 4/24/1971 (Livingstone) (2) (Box 37, Folder 37)
  was b22f18 -- 24 photographs
- Peace Demonstration - Wash. April 1971 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  was b22f19 -- 27 photographs
- Peace Demonstration Bryant Park 5/5/1971 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  was b22f20 -- 10 photographs
- Peace March - Nov. 6, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 40)
  was b22f21 - 12 photographs
- Peace - Labor for Peace - St. Louis - June, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  was b22f22 -- 21 photographs
- Pension Meeting - AIN & Link (Box 37, Folder 42)
  was b22f23 -- 1 photograph
- Persian Lamb Skins (Box 37, Folder 43)
  was b22f24 -- 1 photograph
- Phila. Fur Workers Meeting - 12/8/1985 (Box 37, Folder 44)
  was b22f25 -- 6 photographs
- Photo Exhibit - 1982-1983 (Box 37, Folder 45)
  was b22f26 -- 4 photographs
- Les Pines Performing at Fur Workers Resort (Box 37, Folder 46)
  was b22f27 -- 1 photograph
- Ben Pinsley - Fishing (Box 37, Folder 47)
  was b22f28 - 4 photographs
- Ben Pinsley - Grading on a mink Ranch, Etc. (Box 37, Folder 48)
  was b22f29 -- 5 photographs
- Ben Pinsley Testimonial -- Feb. 13, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 49)
  was b22f30 -- 23 photographs
- Ben Pinsley Testimonial - Feb. 13, 1965 (2) (Box 37, Folder 50)
  was b22f30 -- 11 photographs
- Pires Retirement Party - Resina - Aug. 25, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  was b22f31 -- 7 photographs
- Pocahontas Back Day Tempo - Dec., 1969 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  was b22f32 -- 11 photographs
- Pocahontas Tanning Co. ( Dental) - 3/20/1984 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  was b22f33 - 8 photographs
- Pocahontas Grievance Session (Extra) (Box 38, Folder 4)
  was b22f34 -- 2 photographs
- Pocahontas Tanning Meetings - July 9, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  was b22f35 -- 2 photographs
- Pocahontas Negotiations - Jan. 1981 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  was b22f36 -- 2 photographs
- Pocahontas Tanning Picnic - Aug. 13, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  was b22f37 -- 26 photographs
- Pocahontas Ratification - 1972 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  was b22f38 - 10 photographs
- Pocahontas Safety Awards (Box 38, Folder 9)
  was b22f39 - 1 photographs
- Pocahontas Tanning Strike -- May-June 1984 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  was b22f40
- Police Brutality (Box 38, Folder 11)
  was b22f41 - 3 photographs
- Political Action Committee -- 1/14/1974 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  was b22f42 -- 3 photographs
- Political Action Committee - 4/22/1974 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  was b22f43 -- 4 photographs
- Political Action Committee - Schalhter (Box 38, Folder 14)
  was b22f44 -- 1 photograph
- Political Activities/Rallies (Box 38, Folder 15)
  was b22f45 -- 14 photographs
- Political Economy Class - 2/1976 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  was b22f46 - 7 photographs
- Political Figures (Box 38, Folder 17)
  was b22f47 -- 11 photographs
- Poor People's Campaign - 6/19/1988 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  was b22f48 - 18 photographs
- Portuguese Relief (Box 38, Folder 19)
  was b22f49 -- 4 photographs
- Irving Potash, manager Furriers Joint Council (Box 38, Folder 20)
  was b22f50 -- 12 photographs
- Potash Birthday Ball - Amnesty Telegrams (Box 38, Folder 21)
  was b22f51 -- 6 photographs
- Potash Memorial Meeting -- 10/19/1976 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  was b22f52 -- 1 photograph
- Presentations, Citations, Plaques, etc. (1) (Box 38, Folder 23)
  was b22f53 -- 25 photographs
- Presentations, Citations, Plaques, etc. (2) (Box 38, Folder 24)
  was b22f53 -- 26 photographs
- Presentations, Citations, Plaques, etc. (3) (Box 38, Folder 25)
  was b22f53 -- 10 photographs
- NAT Pressman Retirement Party -- 3/11/1983 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  was b22f54 -- 5 photographs
- Princess Ribbon negotiations - Dec. 1980 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  was b22f55 -- 2 photographs
- Public Affairs Committee - Feb. 4-Mar.4, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  was b22f56 -- 3 photographs
- Puerto Rico Sings (Box 38, Folder 29)
  was b22f57 -- 2 photographs
- Queens Community Labor Committee -- 9/30/1965 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  was b22f58 -- 6 photographs
- Rabbit Negotiations - June 1970 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  was b22f59 -- 2 photographs
- Rabbit Section Negotiations - June 1970 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  was b22f60 -- 4 photographs
- Rabbit Dressers Contract - 6/6/1972 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  was b22f61 -- 1 photograph
- Rabbit Dressers Contract - June 1974 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  was b22f62 -- 2 photographs
- Rabbit Dressers Contract Ratification - 7/1978 (Box 38, Folder 35)
  was b22f63 -- 6 photographs
- Race Relations Class (Box 38, Folder 36)
  was b22f64 -- 7 photographs
- Radel Shop Meeting - April 1969 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  was b22f65 -- 1 photograph
- Railex Negotiations - 1/1982 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  was b22f66 - 2 photographs
- Ratification Mtg. (Box 38, Folder 39)
  was b22f67 - 7 photographs
- Alex Raynes at work (Box 38, Folder 40)
  was b22f68 - 7 photographs
- Alex Raynes Exhibit - 7/1976 (Box 38, Folder 41)
  was b22f69 -- 4 photographs
- Recoton - First Benefit Recipient (Box 38, Folder 42)
  was b22f70 -- 1 photograph
- Recoton Victory Celebration - March 1986 (Box 38, Folder 43)
  was b22f71 - 14 photographs
- Registration - Brooklyn - Queens - Bronx - 5/1974 (Box 38, Folder 44)
  was b22f72 -- 12 photographs
- Pix used in reporter (1) (Box 39, Folder 1)
  was b22f74 - 25 photographs
- Pix used in reporter (2) (Box 39, Folder 2)
  was b22f74 -- 22 photographs
- Resina Shop (Box 39, Folder 3)
  was b22f74 -- photographs
- Resina - Goldsmith Celebration - 1/7/1968 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  was b22f75 -- 1 photograph
- Resina Shop Meeting, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  was b22f76 -- 5 photographs
- Resina Shop Meeting (Box 39, Folder 6)
  was b22f77 -- 1 photograph
- Resina Shop meeting - 11/1981 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  was b22f78 -- 5 photographs
- Resina Xmas Party - 12/19/1981 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  was b22f79 -- 4 photographs
- Resina Contract Negotiations - Nov.-Dec. 1982 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  was b22f80 -- 4 photographs
- Resina Xmas Party - Dec. 29, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  was b22f81 -- 6 photographs
- Resina Contract - Nov. 1983 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  was b22f82 -- 4 photographs
- Resina Xmas Party - Dec. 1983 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  was b22f83 -- 7 photographs
- Resina Holiday Party - Dec. 21, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  was b22f84 -- 2 photographs
- Resina Christmas Party - Dec. 1985 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  was b22f85 -- 2 photographs
- Resina Negotiations - Nov. 1986 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  was b22f86 -- 5 photographs
- Retired Members (Box 39, Folder 16)
  was b22f87 -- 19 photographs
- Retired Members - Anniv. Celebration (Box 39, Folder 17)
  was b22f88 - 20 photographs
- Retired Members - Circle Line Outing (Box 39, Folder 18)
  was b22f89 -- 4 photographs
- Retired Members - Hyde Park Outing (1) (Box 39, Folder 19)
  was b22f90 -- 26 photographs
- Retired Members - Hyde Park Outing (2) (Box 39, Folder 20)
  was b22f90 -- 14 photographs
- Retired Members - Medicare Demonstration (Box 39, Folder 21)
  was b22f91 -- 8 photographs
- Retired Members - Party - 1965 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  was b22f92 -- 2 photographs
- Retired Members - Toys for Bellevue (Box 39, Folder 23)
  was b22f93 -- 7 photographs
- Retired Members - Visit to U.N. (Box 39, Folder 24)
  was b22f94 -- 11 photographs
- Retirees Center (Box 39, Folder 25)
  was b22f95 -- 9 photographs
- Retirees Center (Box 39, Folder 26)
  was b22f96 -- 3 photographs
- Retirees Center (Box 39, Folder 27)
  was b22f97 --
- Retirees Center (Box 39, Folder 28)
  was b22f98 -- 7 photographs
- Retirees Center - Council Choral Group (Box 39, Folder 29)
  was b22f99 -- 1 photograph
- Retirees Center Tribute to Irwin Corey (Box 39, Folder 30)
  was b22f100 -- 20 photographs
- Retirees Center Xmas - New Year's Party - Dec. 26, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  was b22f101 -- 4 photographs
- Retirees Center - UN Program - 3/9/1972 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  was b22f102 -- 1 photograph
- Retirees Center - Oct. 4, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  was b22f103 -- 2 photographs
- Retirees Center - Arrow Park - 6/1974 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  was b22f104 -- 3 photographs
- Retirees Center -- 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  was b22f105 -- 8 photographs
- Retirees Center Party - 12/22/1977 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  was b22f106 -- 2 photographs
- Retirees Center -- 12/1979-1/1980 (Box 39, Folder 37)
  was b22f107 -- 12 photographs
- Retirees Center Holiday Party - Dec. 1980 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  was b22f108 - 5 photographs
- Retirees Center Outing - 6/4/1982 (Box 39, Folder 39)
  was b22f109 -- 16 photographs
- Retirees Center Meeting - 11/18/1982 (Box 39, Folder 40)
  was b22f110 -- 2 photographs
- Retirees Center - 1982-1983 (Box 39, Folder 41)
  was b22f111 -- 28 photographs
- Retirees Center - Fall, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 42)
  was b22f112 -- 21 photographs
- Retirees Center Pictures - 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 43)
  was b22f113 -- 9 photographs
- Retirees Center - Drs. Lomax & Strauss - 5/17/1984 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  was b22f114 -- 11 photographs
- Retirees Center - Oct. 1984 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  was b22f115 -- 10 photographs
- Retirees Center - Dec. 1984 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  was b22f116 -- 12 photographs
- Retirees Xmas Party - 12/1978 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  was b22f117 -- 3 photographs
- Retirees Class on Nutrition (Box 40, Folder 5)
  was b22f118 -- 2 photographs
- Retirees - FLM Joint Board (Box 40, Folder 6)
  was b22f119 -- 20 photographs
- Retirees - Local 63-L -- Elkland, PA (Box 40, Folder 7)
  was b22f120 -- 3 photographs
- Retirees Luncheon FJC -- 10/30/1979 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  was b22f121 -- 9 photographs
- Retirees Luncheons - Florida - 3/1981 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  was b22f122 -- 8 photographs
- Retirees Outing (Box 40, Folder 10)
  was b22f123 -- 4 photographs
- Retirees Outing -- 6/8/1978 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  was b22f124 -- 3 photographs
- Retirees Outing -- 6/12/1980 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  was b22f125 -- 6 photographs
- Retirees Outing -- June 1983 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  was b22f126 -- 6 photographs
- Retirees Outing -- June 20, 1985 #395 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  was b22f127 -- 3 photographs
- Retirees Outing - June 1986 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  was b22f128 -- 15 photographs
- Retirees Picnic, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  was b22f129 -- 15 photographs
- Retirement Center Xmas - Chanukah Party, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  was b22f130 -- 3 photographs
- Retirement Luncheons (1) (Box 40, Folder 18)
  was b22f131 -- 26 photographs
- Retirement Luncheon (2) (Box 40, Folder 19)
  was b22f131 -- 6 photographs
- Revillon Freres Workers - Feb. 13, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  was b22f132 -- 1 photograph
- Hyman Richman Bus. Agent FJC (Box 40, Folder 21)
  was b22f133 -- 2 photographs
- Romero Metals Shop Meeting (Box 40, Folder 22)
  was b22f134 -- 1 photograph
- Russian War Relief (Box 40, Folder 23)
  was b22f135 -- 6 photographs
- Safety and Health Class - Jan. 1983 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  was b22f136 -- 5 photographs
- Max Salzman Memorial - Sept. 26 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  was b22f137 -- 7 photographs
- Ollie Samuels Commencement - June 1985 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  was b22f138 -- 2 photographs
- Sands Arbitration - Nov. 1, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  was b22f139 -- 2 photographs
- Wesley Scarlett (Box 40, Folder 28)
  was b22f140 -- 1 photograph
- Henrietta Schaffner Testimonial Dinner - June 8, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  was b22f141 -- 4 photographs
- Senior Citizens Council of N.Y. (Box 40, Folder 30)
  was b22f142 -- 3 photographs
- Senior Citizens Rally on COLA - 5/16/1985 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  was b22f143 - 1 photograph
- SETON (Box 40, Folder 32)
  was b22f144 -- 5 photographs
- SETON - Monk - Baseball Game -- 6/27/1981 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  was b22f145 -- 12 photographs
- SETON contract - 6/1979 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  was b22f146 -- 8 photographs
- SETON Demands Meeting - Jan. 1972 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  was b22f147 -- 11 photographs
- SETON Leather Classes - 11/21/1985 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  was b22f148 -- 1 photographs
- SETON Leather Grievance Session (Box 40, Folder 37)
  was b22f149 -- 1 photograph
- SETON Leather Negotiations & Benefit Meeting (Box 40, Folder 38)
  was b22f150 -- 5 photographs
- SETON Leather Negotiations & Ratification Meeting - May, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  was b22f151 -- 20 photographs
- SETON Leather Postcard Signing 6/1983 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  was b22f152 -- 2 photographs
- SETON Shop Meeting 1976 (Box 40, Folder 41)
  was b22f153 -- 8 photographs
- SETON Leather Shop Meeting 3/1979 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  was b22f154 -- 24 photographs
- SETON Leather - Toggler's Grievance (Box 40, Folder 43)
  was b22f155 -- 1 photograph
- Sewing Machine Project (Box 40, Folder 44)
  was b22f156 -- 5 photographs
- Sewing Machine Negotiations, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 45)
  was b22f157 -- 1 photograph
- Sewing Machine Section Meeting Oct. 6, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 46)
  was b22f158 -- 6 photographs
- Sewing Machine Pensioners - May 1970 (Box 40, Folder 47)
  was b22f159 -- 2 photographs
- Sewing Machine Section Meeting - June 1972 (Box 40, Folder 48)
  was b22f160 -- 16 photographs
- Sewing Machine Section Meetings - 9/1974 (Box 40, Folder 49)
  was b22f161 -- 4 photographs
- Sewing Machine Negotiations - 3/1977 (Box 40, Folder 50)
  was b22f162 -- 6 photographs
- Sewing Machine Section Contract - 3/1983 (Box 40, Folder 51)
  was b22f163 -- 6 photographs
- Sewing Machine Section Ratification - March 1986 (Box 40, Folder 52)
  was b22f164 -- 4 photographs
- Shapson - Local 48 (Box 40, Folder 53)
  was b22f165 -- 2 photographs
- Shapson Meeting -- 5/30/1972 (Box 40, Folder 54)
  was b22f166 -- 29 photographs
- Shapson Shop Meetings - 5/10/1973 (Box 40, Folder 55)
  was b22f167 -- 1 photograph
- Shapson Retirees - 7/1973 (Box 40, Folder 56)
  was b22f168 -- 7 photographs
- Shapson Negotiating Committee -- 11/1973 (Box 40, Folder 57)
  was b22f169 -- 1 photograph
- Shapson, Inc. May-1974; Aug. 1974 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  was b22f170 - 1 photograph
- Shapson Meeting - 3/6/1975 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  was b22f171 -- 2 photographs
- Shapson Shop Meeting -- 11/16/1976 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  was b22f172 -- 12 photographs
- Shapson Negotiations - 1976 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  was b22f173 -- 10 photographs
- Shapson Ratification Meeting - Aug. 1978 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  was b22f174 -- 13 photographs
- Sheltered Workshop - PA -- Nov. 1971 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  was b23f1 - 4 photographs
- Sam Sherman Testimonial -- June 1974 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  was b23f2 - 1 photograph
- Leon Shlofrock (Box 41, Folder 8)
  was b23f3 - 2 photographs
- Unlabeled (1) (Box 41, Folder 9)
  was b23f4 - 26 photographs
- Unlabeled (2) (Box 41, Folder 10)
  was b23f4 -- 26 photographs
- Unlabeled (3) (Box 41, Folder 11)
  was b23f4 -- 7 photographs
- Shop Chairmen's Conference (1) (Box 41, Folder 12)
  was b23f5 -- 26 photographs
- Shop Chairmen's Conference (2) (Box 41, Folder 13)
  was b23f5 -- 11 photographs
- Shorter Work Week Committee (Box 41, Folder 14)
  was b23f6 -- 1 photograph
- Shorter Work Week founding Meeting - 10/27/1977 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  was b23f7 -- 5 photographs
- Shorter Work Week Meeting - 4/11/1978 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  was b23f8 -- 1 photographs
- Silk Section Meeting - 3/1972 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  was b23f9 -- 1 photograph
- Silverman Testimonial - 4/14/1972 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  was b23f10 -- 4 photographs
- Sol Silverman Tribute - 12/5/1978 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  was b23f11 -- 1 photograph
- Singer Negotiations Material (Box 41, Folder 20)
  was b23f12 -- 20 photographs
- N.G. Slater Contract Settlement - 3/1983 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  was b23f13 -- 2 photographs
- Gladstone Smith Retirement Party - 5/13/1974 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  was b23f14 -- 3 photographs
- Smith & Weigler Liquidation (Box 41, Folder 23)
  was b23f15 -- 3 photographs
- Social Security Demonstration (Box 41, Folder 24)
  was b23f16 -- 2 photographs
- South Africa Demonstrations Dec. 1984 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  was b23f17 -- 3 photographs
- South Florida Retirees -- 11/19/1979 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  was b23f18 -- 7 photographs
- South Florida Reunion - Feb. 7, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  was b23f19 -- 1 photograph
- Soviet Trade Unionists visit - 11/1977 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  was b23f20 -- 1 photograph
- Spain - Congressional Conference - 6/10/1975 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  was b23f21 -- 2 photographs
- Spanish Board Members, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  was b23f22 -- 1 photograph
- Sports Program (Box 41, Folder 31)
  was b23f23 -- 7 photographs
- Sports Program - Jan. 1981 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  was b23f24 - 2 photographs
- Sports/Recreation (Box 41, Folder 33)
  was b23f25 -- 21 photographs
- Staff Meeting Locals 1-3 -- 3/18/1987 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  was b23f26 -- 2 photographs
- Steel Equipment Negotiations - Dec. 1980 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  was b23f27 -- 6 photographs
- Steel Partition Section Meeting - Jan. 1970 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  was b23f28 -- 2 photographs
- Steel Partition Meeting - 12/23/1974 (Box 41, Folder 37)
  was b23f29 -- 9 photographs
- Steel Partition Section Meeting - 10/1977 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  was b23f30 -- 4 photographs
- Steel Participation Negotiations - Dec. 1983 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  was b23f31 -- 4 photographs
- Steel Partition Negotiations -- Dec. - Jan. 1987 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  was b23f32 -- 11 photographs
- Stephenson & Osborne Ratification - Nov. 1971 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  was b23f33 - 8 photographs
- Henry Stern at FLM - 10/1977 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  was b23f34 -- 1 photograph
- Stern Weekend Tribute - 9/8/1978 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  was b23f35 -- 7 photographs
- Mark Straus Retirement Luncheon (Box 42, Folder 5)
  was b23f36
- Street Scenes (Box 42, Folder 6)
  was b23f37 -- 25 photographs
- Strike Support (Box 42, Folder 7)
  was b23f38 -- 10 photographs
- Sudanese Trade Union Delegation - Aug. 1984 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  was b23f39 -- 3 photographs
- Supelt Workers' Children at Beth Israel Hospital, Newark (Box 42, Folder 9)
  was b23f40 -- 6 photographs
- Superior Dyed Furs Shop Meeting, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  was b23f41 -- 1 photograph
- Superior Pet Contract Ratification, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  was b23f42 -- 1 photograph
- Superior Pet Grievances (Box 42, Folder 12)
  was b23f43 -- 4 photographs
- Superior Pet Negotiating Committee 3/1972 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  was b23f44 -- 4 photographs
- Superior Pet Negotiating Committee - 9/1973 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  was b23f45 -- 1 photograph
- Superior Pet Nominating Meeting - 4/17/1984 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  was b23f46 -- 2 photographs
- Supply Section Negotiations - 2/1984 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  was b23f47 photographs -- 2 photographs
- Tanners Cut Sole Negotiations - Nov. 1983 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  was b23f48 -- 3 photographs
- Tanners Cut Sole Party -- Dec. 1984 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  was b23f49 -- 5 photographs
- TEC - Cast Meeting -- 12/9/1985 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  was b23f50 -- 4 photographs
- Tenant Rally -- Oct. 5, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  was b23f51 -- 1 photograph
- Tenant's Unity Day 10/5/1980 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  was b23f52 -- 1 photograph
- Tetley Tea - Raglan George (Box 42, Folder 22)
  was b23f53 -- 2 photographs
- Tetley Tea -- April 1977 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  was b23f54 -- 2 photographs
- Tetley Meeting - 5/19/1977 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  was b23f55 - 1 photograph
- Tetley Ratification - 11/1977 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  was b23f56 -- 5 photographs
- Tetley Meeting -- 9/1980 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  was b23f57 -- 10 photographs
- Tetley Tea Shop Meeting -- 11/7/1982 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  was b23f58 -- 10 photographs
- Tetley Contract 9/1983 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  was b23f59 -- 3 photographs
- Tetley Grievance Session -- Oct. 1983 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  was b23f60 -- 1 photograph
- Tetley Nominating Meeting 4/1984 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  was b23f61 -- 3 photographs